http://virusall.com/privacy.php

no link
[ Shop ]
1. Personal Information
No web page at 'Virus or Hoax?' requires our visitors to provide any kind of personal information.
2. Email
'Virus or Hoax?' considers email transmitted via our service to be private correspondence between the sender and recipient. Therefore, we will not monitor, edit or disclose the contents of your private communications. The sender email address remains private and is not collected nor distributed to third parties.
3. Passive Data Collection
'Virus or Hoax?' is not using or intending to use any form of data collection related to our visitors. No recording, tracking or any other form of registration of our visitors IP address or browsing preferences will take place.
4. Cookies
Cookies enable a web site to tailor information presented to you based on your browsing preferences. 'Virus or Hoax?' is not using cookies. You can verify this by setting your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software.
Cookies used by external web sites to categorize your visite are not the responsibility of 'Virus or Hoax?'.
5. Web Site Traffic
Web site traffic is used to track traffic patterns through 'Virus or Hoax?'. This may include domain names, IP addresses and browser types. This information is not correlated with any personal information.
6. Links
This site contains links to other sites. 'Virus or Hoax?' is not responsible for the privacy practices of these web sites. 'Virus or Hoax?' is not responsible for any content on any linked sites or for any goods or services available from them.
7. Privacy Policy Changes
'Virus or Hoax?' reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
Updated: February 20th, 2005 - March 14th, 2009.
Advertising
Use 'DHL for You' for easy package sending in the Netherlands!
Save 10% off top Norton Products with Coupon Code 10NAMNORTONSTORE
Save now - 25% off - 2 year license of ESET NOD32 Antivirus 4
Save 20% on Trend Micro™
Titanium™ Maximum Security! Coupon Code: titanium20
Norton 360 Version 5.0 3 Year Protection
ZoneAlarm Internet Security Suite 2012 - Save 50%
Copyright (c) 1997 - 2012 virusall.com. All rights reserved.
Disclaimer - Privacy Policy - Contact
b82edc04728096d9b7a600176c728337
